你聽到了嗎 我找不到手機了
Do you hear that? I can't find my phone.
聽起來像是從水果碗里傳出來的
I think it's coming from the fruit bowl.
不要啊
Oh, no.
我又開始夢游變魔術了
I've been doing sleep magic again.
你看起來像完全沒睡過覺
You look like you haven't slept at all.
可能一晚就只睡了一兩小時吧
Maybe an hour or two a night.
我什么都試過了
I've tried everything:
睡前的熱水澡 冥想
warm shower before bed, meditation,
閱讀我手機操作系統的用戶協議
reading my operating system's user agreement.
你有沒有試過問艾麗克斯
Did you try asking Alex about the struggles that are unique
女性在科學領域所特有的掙扎
to women in science?
昨晚深夜時候問的 她好像還沒講完
Late last night. I think she's still going.
這失眠時機太糟糕了
It's the worst possible timing.
我今天要為一個重要的待售屋拍廣告
I have a video shoot for a big listing today,
而且我也得上鏡
and I'm supposed to be on camera.
我得走了
I gotta go.
爸爸 你的鑰匙
Dad, your keys.
我來開車吧
You know what? I'll drive.
祝你面試順利
Good luck with your interview.
你猜怎么著 我決定不去了
Oh, you know what? I decided to pass on that.
為什么
Why?
那是個很棒的工作 你之前表現得很期待啊
That's an amazing job, and you were so excited.
我想那只是我感到受寵若驚吧
I think I was flattered.
就像你去酒吧 有人送來一杯酒那樣
Like when you go to a bar and a guy sends you a drink.
我不懂好嗎 我在國內頂尖的科技大學讀書
I'm at the leading scientific university in the country.
里面的宅男連他們機器人的眼睛都不敢直視
Those guys can't even look their robots in the eye.
我被邀請去"內德叔叔餅干"面試首席執行官職位
I was asked to interview for CEO of Uncle Ned's Cookies,
那公司是休閑食品行業的重量級選手
a major player in the snack food industry.
這個職位空缺原來是因為
The position opened up because it turns out
內德叔叔喜歡在工作時玩弄...
Uncle Ned liked to play fast and loose with...
他的生殖器
his genitals at work.
媽媽 你需要參加這場面試
Mom, you need to take that interview.
現在人們正在把雄性渣滓
Now that they're purging male creeps
清除出行政職位
from executive positions,
強大的女性終得在談判桌上占有一席之地
strong women are finally getting their seat at the table.
親愛的 我已經有一席之地了
Honey, I already have a seat at the table.
實際上 我在談判桌的主位呢
In fact, at the head of the table.
你是說當外公不在時嗎
You mean when Grandpa's not there?
談判桌有兩個主位
Tables have two heads.
我只是說出了我標志性的殘酷事實
I'm only bringing out my trademark hard truths
因為我不想讓你放棄
because I don't want you to pass up
在父權制順從社會中出頭的絕佳機會
an amazing opportunity in deference to the patriarchy.
寶貝 我現在的工作里有許多絕佳機會
Honey, I have a lot of amazing opportunities at my current job.
而且"內德叔叔"不都是抽大麻的人在吃的嗎
And isn't Uncle Ned's basically just stoner food?
我們愛"內德叔叔"
We love Uncle Ned's!
我好想念它們
I miss those.
謝謝你的關心 不過我會沒事的
Thank you for your concern, but I'll be fine.
也許我只是在發泄我自己
Maybe I'm just projecting my own frustrations
在科學界的挫折感
with the science world.
你知道嗎 那里只有三名女博士
You know, there are only three female PhDs --
甜心 很抱歉 我得保持清醒不能犯困
Sweetheart, I'm sorry, but I have to stay alert.
莉莉寶貝 開門 上學要遲到了
Lily, sweetie, open up. We're gonna be late for school.
我不去上學 別管我
I'm not going! Leave me alone!
-另一個危機 -她把自己鎖浴室里了
- Another meltdown. - She's locked herself in the bathroom.
現在你后悔當初沒讓我在后院建茅房了吧
Now don't you wish you'd let me build that outhouse?
不后悔
Still no.
她 她怎么了
W-What is going on with her?
她最近變得好情緒化
S-She's been so moody recently,
前一分鐘還在尖叫 下一分鐘就哭了
screaming one minute, crying the next.
我想我知道這是什么情況了
You know what? I think I know what this might be.
她要在今天的科學課上交一座火山模型
She had a volcano due in science class today,
我在她這年紀時 肩負重任的話
and when I was her age and had a big project,
我會焦慮不安 表現得和這一樣
I'd get stressed out and act just like this.
你知道嗎 我到現在都還在做
You know, I still have nightmares about
當年北方侵略戰爭模型的噩夢
my War of Northern Aggression diorama.
好了 我們結婚時說了什么
Okay. What did we say when we got married?
永遠不帶著怒氣上床
Never go to bed angry
以及叫它內戰 而不是北方侵略你們南方
and you have to call it the Civil War.
好了 我去看看她作業做到什么程度了
Okay, I'll go check and see how far she's gotten.
好 莉莉寶貝 出來吧 好嗎
Okay, Lily, honey, come on. Come out, all right?
我們能幫你修好你的火山
We can help you fix your volcano,
你還是能來得及上學的
and -- and you'll still make it to school.
最壞的結果不過就是
Worst comes to worst,
第一節課[初潮]稍稍遲到一點
you'll be a little late for your first period.
其實 她可能"早到"了
Actually, she's a little early.
所以...
So --
莉莉現在是個月經者了
Lily is a menstruator now.
不是那樣叫的
That's not what you call it.
我只是有點羞于承認
Well, I'm just ashamed to admit
我們從未幫她準備過這個
that we never really prepared her for it.
我們曾經試過一次
Hey, we tried that one time.
姑娘 你好啊
Hey, girl. Hey!
寶貝 小爸和我在想
So, sweetie, Daddy and I were wondering if,
既然你開始穿少女文胸了
now that you're wearing a training bra,
如果你對自己正在改變的身體還有其他疑問
if you had any other questions about your changing body.
我們能不說這個嗎
Can we just not?
-聽起來不錯 -好極了
- Sounds good. - Yeah, perfect.
我以為你會請克萊爾
I thought you were gonna ask Claire
跟莉莉說說這個
to talk to Lily about this.
我有嘗試 但當時克萊爾心情很不好
Well, I was, but when I tried, Claire was in such a mood,
因為諷刺的是[更年期]...
because, ironically...
我們不能搞砸 不能讓她有心理陰影
Okay, we can't screw this up. We cannot give her a complex.
你看看能不能聯系到克萊爾
Okay, you see if you can track down Claire.
我會去藥房
I will go to the pharmacy
試著克服我對女性護理用品通道的恐懼
and try and conquer my fear of the feminine care aisle.
可憐的莉莉
Poor Lily.
還可能更糟
You know, it could be worse.
如果她是羊 每十七天都要這樣一次
If she were a sheep, she'd be dealing with this every 17 days.
答應我 我不在時你不會這樣說
Promise you won't say that while I'm gone.
好了 我們再來試試包襁褓
All right, let's try the swaddle again.
把毛毯折成三角狀
Our blankets are folded into triangles,
左邊折一下
we do a left tuck,
下面折一下
a toe tuck,
右邊折一下
a right tuck,
然后大功告成 嬰兒卷餅就好啦
and voila, baby burrito.
你是怎么包成功的
Ugh! How did you do yours?!
那個暑假在地下室卷餅小作坊工作
I guess that summer working at Burrito Basement
感染大腸桿菌 現在終于值得了
was worth the E. Coli.
迪蘭和我正在上嬰兒護理課程
Dylan and I have been taking a baby care class.
很令人沮喪 因為即使他缺了一些課
It's frustrating, because even though he's missed some,
成績也能大殺四方
he's crushing it.
是說課程啦 不是練習用的寶寶
The class, not the practice doll.
殺寶寶的人是我
That was me.
繼續吧 我們今天還要練習什么
Let's move on.What else do we have to get down for today?
-拍嗝 -太好了
- Burping. - Great!
我拍拍拍 嗝 還有什么
A bur-bur-burp. Boom. What's next?
等等 媽媽
Hold on, Mom.
你還記得萬一過肩拍不管用時
Do you remember the four other methods
其他的四種方法嗎
in case over-the-shoulder doesn't work?
其中一招是找人把他嚇出嗝嗎
Uh, was one scare 'em?
還有放在大腿上拍
There's over-the-lap,
膝上拍
over-the-knee,
奶奶式拍 和蹦蹦拍
Grandmother's burp, and the bounce burp.
為什么我學這么慢啊
Ugh. Why do I suck at this?
我理解這內容很多 不過你會慢慢學會的
I know it's overwhelming, but you're gonna get there.
別擔心
Don't worry.
別炫耀了
Stop showing off.
太好了 你在這坐著呢
Oh, good. You're sitting down.
我們有個問題
We have a problem.
我上公司官網 發現有人
I went on the company website, and somebody left off
取消了總裁級柜的磨砂銅升級
the brushed brass upgrade on the Executive Premiere.
是的是的 我停止磨砂銅升級了
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I eighty-sixed that.
可是我已經簽署同意了
I already signed off on it.
可能他們后來又想來跟我確認一下
They probably just wanted to double-check with me.
你也知道 我確實有三十年的經驗
You know, I do have 30 years' experience.
《櫥柜時代周刊》曾經稱我為
Closet Time Magazine once called me
"存儲空間[太空]競賽中的尼爾·阿姆斯特朗"
"The Neil Armstrong of the storage space race."
得了吧 爸 你一周就工作兩天
Okay, Dad, you work two days a week,
上次員工會議還全程涂鴉
and you spent the entire last staff meeting
畫菠蘿
doodling a pineapple.
這么著吧 你掌管伯克郡生產線
How about this -- take the helm on the Berkshire line.
我中斷那個項目了
I discontinued that.
是這樣沒錯 不過后來杰夫在洗手間逼我
Yeah, but then Jeff cornered me in the men's room,
我又重啟了
and I relaunched it.
好吧 爸 你這樣讓我十分難做
Okay, Dad, you are putting me in an impossible position.
我做完決定 一個轉身你就推翻我的決定
I make decisions, and then you go around undermining them.
這里的大家都很重視你的看法 克萊爾
Everybody values your opinions around here, Claire.
事實上 我現在就需要你的看法
In fact, I'd like your opinion right now.
這個看著像個冰屋嗎
Does this look like an igloo?
內德叔叔餅干公司想讓我去當首席執行官
Uncle Ned's Cookies wants me to be their CEO.
什么 你在考慮去內德叔叔公司
What?! You're considering Uncle Ned's?!
你嗑藥嗑高了嗎
Are you on reefer?!
那家公司有巨大的增長潛力
That company has tremendous growth potential.
那只是零食 這可是衣柜
It's snacks! This is closets!
你現在已經在大舞臺上了
You're already at the show!
至少在那里 我能做老板
At least there, I can be the boss
而不只是老板的女兒
and not just the boss's daughter.
所以現在是到了我跟你道歉
Is this the part where I apologize
抱歉把曾經被《高級衣柜雜志》
for handing you a company
稱為"頂層"的公司交給你的環節嗎
Closet Fancy once called "Top shelf"?!
不 是到了我要去參加面試
No, this is the part where I take an interview
跟那些能真正認同我價值的人共事的環節
with people who actually recognize my value!
靜音滑動門都摔不出氣勢
Damn whisper slides.
莉莉還在衛生間嗎
Is Lily still in the bathroom?
你說呢 我用貓砂上廁所是為了好玩嗎
No, I used Larry's cat box for fun.
真的假的 她需要這么多嗎
Okay. Really? She needed all of this?
太多選擇我不知如何是好
It was totally overwhelming.
我把能拿的都拿了
I just -- I just grabbed as much as I could.
這里有衛生棉條 衛生巾 各種尺寸
I have tampons, maxi pads, variety packs --
對了 還有這個叫女王[月經]杯的東西
oh, and this thing called a Diva Cup,
聽起來感覺很可愛就買了
'cause, I don't know, sounded kind of cute.
那 我們現在該做什么
So, what are we supposed to do?
總不能把這些盒子丟過去祝她好運吧
We can't just throw these boxes in there and wish her good luck.
感謝上帝
Oh, thank God.
那是克萊爾嗎 你聯系她了嗎
Is that Claire? Did you reach her?
不是 她沒有回復 所以我呼叫了后援
No, she wasn't answering, so I -- I called for backup.
謝謝你們讓我參與到這個特別的時刻
Thank you for including me in this special time.
我帶來了花 因為我們的莉莉正如花般盛開
I brought flowers because our Lily's blossoming!
好 我們真的非常感謝你來幫忙
Well, we really appreciate you helping us out.
應該的
Of course.
這就是家里有個女人的好處了
This is when it's good to have a woman in the house.
我完全沒有說兩個男人養育女兒
Not that two men raising a daughter
是違背自然規律的意思
is unnatural in any way.
我很確定剛才完全沒人想到這個
Pretty sure no one was thinking that.
抱歉 我慌了手腳 群發了信息
Sorry -- I-I panicked and sent a group text
因為不知道誰會回復
because I didn't know who would respond.
你們好啊 我給莉莉帶了知識小冊子
Hey. I brought Lily some pamphlets.
理解生理知識能讓她
Understanding the biology will help make her
更坦然面對自己的小經經
more comfortable with her menses.
"小精精" 快來人把小個子同志酒吧叫這個啊
Mensies? How is that not a gay bar for little men?
-我們應該... -我們不會再買一個域名了
- We should-- - We're not buying another domain name.
她不需要生理知識冊子
She doesn't need pamphlets.
她需要的是愛和支持
She needs love and support.
這是一場美妙的儀式
It's a beautiful rite of passage
將把她和每一個女人聯結起來
that is going to connect her with women everywhere.
別那么詩意了 疼起來要命的
Let's not get poetic. It hurts like hell.
所以我帶了給她做傳統哥倫比亞
And that's why I brought all the ingredients
月經藥糊的所有材料
to make her a traditional Colombian period poultice,
等她痛經的時候可以敷在肚子上
and she can rub it on her belly when she gets cramps.
或者她吃點布洛芬就好了
Or she could just take some ibuprofen.
但是那能消除她的罪孽嗎
Oh, but is that going to draw out all of her sins?
因為罪孽就是女人有月經最根本的原因
'Cause that's why women get their period in the first place.
好吧 很有用 兩種方法都很有價值
Okay, very helpful. Two equally worthy paths.
我還是更傾向于知識小冊子
Yeah, gotta say I'm leaning toward the pamphlet.
你們好 莉莉怎么樣了
Hey, how's Lily?
太好了 新的聲音
Oh, great -- more voices.
她在哪
Where is she?
-她還把自己鎖在衛生間呢 -真倒霉
- She's still locked in the bathroom. - Damn it!
我肚子里的兩個胎兒正在踢我的膀胱
I have two fetuses kicking me in the bladder,
我真的很需要上廁所
and I really have to pee!
好吧 拉里的貓砂盆在走廊上
Okay, well, Larry's litter box is on the porch.
她懷孕了 你不能讓個孕婦去外面
She's pregnant! You can't ask her to go outside
-蹲貓廁所... -馬上回來
- and squat ov-- - Be right back!
惡心
Gross!
你也沒比我們強多少 你知道吧
You're not better than us, you know.
你覺得自己為什么會睡不著覺呢
Why do you think you're not sleeping?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我覺得是有太多煩心事
I guess I got a lot on my mind.
賬單 有一根腳趾麻痹了
Bills, my one numb toe,
海莉會不會成為一個糟糕的媽媽
is Haley gonna be a terrible mom,
全球變暖
global warming...
慢著慢著 往回倒帶
Back up, back up, back up.
哪根腳趾頭麻
Which toe is numb?
左腳 去市場的那只小豬
Left foot. The one that goes to market.
那你為什么擔心海莉
And why are you worried about Haley?
她在育兒課上看起來沒準備好
At her baby class, she did not seem ready.
迪蘭今天得去上班我挺高興的
I'm kind of glad Dylan had to work today.
我特別想看看你學了多少東西
I'm excited to see what you've learned.
好了 大家 上課前先快速復習一下
Okay, everybody. Quick review before we start.
我們從寶寶多大起可以喂固體食物
At what age can you first give babies solid food?
-六個月 -兩年
- Six months. - Two years!
寶寶睡覺時 你該讓他怎樣躺著
And when you put baby down to sleep, you place him on his...
-仰面躺著 -躺在床墊上
- Back. - Mattress.
囟門是指
And the fontanelle is...
-顱骨間隙 -邁阿密的酒店
- Soft spot. - A hotel in Miami?
菲爾 準備好賣房子了嗎
Phil. You ready to sell a house?
是的是的 我們開始吧
Yes. Yes. Let's do this.
德斯蒙德 這是我的主管盧克
Uh, Desmond, this is my director, Luke.
我是你兒子
I'm your son.
你永遠是我的好兒子
Aww. You always will be.
-爸 -高端房地產
- Dad. - Desmond is the brains
最佳的售房視頻都是出自德斯蒙德之手
behind the best high-end real-estate walkthrough videos.
他幫忙賣出的房子比
He's helped move more houses than, um...
比
than, uh...
總引發地震的那個裂縫叫什么來著
What's the-what's the crack that...causes all the earthquakes?
圣安德烈亞斯斷層
The San Andreas fault.
真好笑
That's funny.
好了 回顧一下我們所討論的
So, to recap our discussion,
開拍后攝像機沿著走道下移
we'll start with the camera coming down the walk.
你開門
You open the door,
說"歡迎來到峽谷嶺道15683號
say "Welcome to 15683 Canyon Ridge Drive,
六臥 七衛 七百九十九平方米
a six-bedroom, seven-bathroom, 8,600 square-foot home
有名望的郵政編碼90212"
in the prestigious 90212 ZIP code."
記住了嗎
You got it?
記住了
I got it.
很好 先拍一條試試
Good. Let's try one.
開始
Here we go.
準備
Ready, and...
開拍
action.
-停 -下一個鏡頭
- Cut. - Moving on?
不
N-no.
不 你全沒記住
No, that wasn't right at all.
我很肯定我沒記錯
Um... pretty sure it was.
菲爾
Phil.
你得把詞全說了
You've got to do the whole thing.
是的 當然
Oh, yes. Yeah, of course.
是啊
Yeah.
從頭開始
Back to one.
準備
Ready, and...
開拍
action.
謝謝
Thank you.
克萊爾 多謝你過來
Claire! Thanks for coming in.
我是本 這是我兄弟埃文
I'm Ben. This is my brother, Evan.
我們老爸就是內德叔叔
Our dad's Uncle Ned.
不過我們只叫他爸
But we just call him Dad.
你能來我們很高興
We are so happy you're here.
多謝你們邀請我
Well, thank you so much for having me.
不得不說 這里真好聞
And can I say -- it smells amazing in here!
是餅干的香味
It's the cookies.
是啊
Yeah.
從財政上講
We are so very impressed
我們對貴衣柜公司的業績十分欽佩
with what your closet company has done, fiscally speaking.
說句公道話 公司是我爸創立的
Well, to be fair, my dad is the one who built the business.
這點我們很有共鳴
We can relate to that.
但我們是指在你加入后
But we mean since you joined.
人們都說公司是從那以后真正發展起來的
Many people are saying that's when it really took off.
能得到認可真好
It is so nice to be recognized.
我認為這家公司有巨大的發展潛力
I-I see tremendous growth potential in this company.
我們也這么認為
We think so.
但得靠優秀的船長駛舵才行
That is, with the right captain steering the ship,
從財政上講
fiscally speaking.
所以我們預備為你提供豐厚薪水
Which is why we're prepared to offer you a big salary,
股票什么的
stock stuff...
你想吃多少餅干就吃多少
And all the cookies you can eat.
我沒想到進展會這么快
I didn't expect this to be going so fast.
其實我們時間不多
Well, we're kind of on a clock.
你瞧 國稅局說我們的一些賬目
You see, the IRS has called some of our bookkeeping...
"赤裸裸地違法"
"Flagrantly illegal."
怎么會發生這種事
How could that happen?
我們正指望你來告訴我們原因
We were hoping you could tell us.
我們對生意一無所知
We don't know anything about business.
-從財政上講 -是的
- Fiscally speaking? - Yeah.
沒錯
Exactly.
那些都是我們老爸在管
That was kind of our dad's thing.
還有生產啊 銷售啊 那些玩意
Also, making them, selling them, all that other stuff.
為明確起見 二位的職務是...
Just to be clear, what are your roles here?
我們過去負責嘗餅干
We used to taste the cookies,
但現在我們是董事局主席了
but now we're chairmen of the board.
我懂了
I see.
作為董事長 我們有法律義務告訴你
As such, we are legally bound to mention
我們和食藥管理局有點情況
a little situation we have with the FDA.
都怪埃文
Thanks to Evan,
有個"毛發百萬分比"總檢測不合格
we keep failing something called the "Hairs-per-million test."
由于我們父親被錄下影像證據
And due to the videotaped evidence against our father,
我們需要一位你這樣的高素質女性
we need a highly qualified woman such as yourself
在國會面前作證
to testify in front of Congress.
二位 這一時讓人很難接受
Uh...guys, this is a lot to take in.
我想我們知道你這話什么意思
Well, I think we know what that means.
是啊
Yeah.
歡迎成為內德叔叔的一員
Welcome to Uncle Ned's.
無論你是單身漢 夫妻或一夾人
Whether you're a bachelor, a couple, or a flamily --
"一夾人" 我剛才說的是"一夾人"
"flamily" -- I just said "flamily."
等等 是"一夾人"嗎
Wait, is it "flamily"?
好吧
All right.
我們從這句開始
Let's just take it from,
"這是現代加州生活的最高水準"
"This is modern California living at its finest."
開拍
And action.
這是現代加州生活的最高水準
This is modern California living at its finest.
停 你又變成英國口音了
Stop! You're doing the British accent again.
我沒聽出來
I'm not hearing it!
開拍
And action.
您將享有最先進的
You'll have state-of-the-art...
電氣用具
appliances --
抱歉 我能行
I'm sorry. I got this.
想象一下從這個視角看到的生活
Imagine life from this perspective.
那玩意要撞上我了
That thing is gonna hit me!
最棒的是 整棟房子都是自動化的
And best of all, the entire house is fully automated.
你用手機就能啟動美麗的噴泉
You can turn on the gorgeous fountains right from your phone.
靠 怎么不靈了
Shoot. They're not working.
我又能感覺到那根腳趾了
Hey, I can feel my toe!
這本則是關于能引起
And this one is about hormonal fluctuations
激烈情緒波動的荷爾蒙波動
that can cause radical mood swings.
前一秒 你還好好的 下一秒
One minute, you're totally fine, and then the next,
-你就... -滾回家吧 死書呆
- you're just -- - Go home, nerd!
...沖想幫你的人發火
...lashing out when someone is trying to help you.
謝謝你幫忙
Okay, well, thank you for helping,
你別放在心上
and don't take it personally.
至少現在我們知道她為什么說我的招牌反折袖口
At least now we know why she called my signature cuffs
比《雨中曲》女主角黛比·雷諾茲的博物館還俗氣
tackier than the Debbie Reynolds museum.
對 絕對是因為荷爾蒙波動才攻擊你的袖口
Y-Yes, that was definitely the hormones talking.
你們把這事看得太嚴重了
Look, everyone's taking this whole thing way too seriously.
等我女兒的第一次"鯊魚嗜血周"到來時
When my daughter has her first Shark Week,
我們只會一笑置之
we're just gonna laugh about it.
女孩們就希望這樣
That's what girls want.
畢竟下面
I mean, it is bananas
每個月發生的場面都驚心動魄
what happens down there every month.
唯一的好處是 月經提醒我該付賬單了
Only good thing is, it reminds me to pay my bills.
難怪懷孕后 我的信用卡一直刷不了
Oh, that's why my credit card keeps getting denied.
如果你有別的地方要去...
Hey, if there's somewhere you need to be --
看老娘的
Just watch this.
婊子
Hey, bitch.
海莉也來了嗎
Haley's here?!
沒錯 而且你高興點
That's right. And cheer up.
你要錯過這件慘事帶來的唯一好處了
You're missing the whole silver lining in all of this.
無論你做錯什么 月經都是你的免死金牌
A period is a Get Out Of Jail Free card for everything.
考試前沒復習
Didn't study for a test?
"人家經痛嘛"
"Oh, wah. I have cramps."
不想上體育課
Don't want to go to gym class?
"抱歉 來例假啦"
"Sorry -- lady problems."
想吃掉整個大蛋糕 中途叫停不愉快的約會
Wanna eat a whole sheet cake? Shut down a bad date?
把大麻裝進棉條盒子里 偷帶進演唱會
Smuggle some weed into a concert in your tampon box?
不會有人檢查棉條盒的
Ain't nobody looking in there.
你有什么毛病啊
What is wrong with you?!
你就想給你女兒這種建議嗎
That's the advice you want to give your daughter?!
我知道 我真是糟透了
I know! I'm a disaster!
我要怎么當人媽媽 我連襁褓都不會包
How am I going to be a mother? I can't even make a swaddle!
我會養出兩個廢物 就像我一樣
I'm gonna raise a couple losers, just like me!
不是你們的錯 可愛的小笨蛋們
It's not your fault, you sweet dummies!
莉莉
Lily!
老天 你也來了
Oh, my God. You too?
我給你熬了哥倫比亞藥糊
I made you a Colombian poultice.
就是那玩意發出臭味嗎 我聞到想吐
Is that what stinks? It's making me sick!
我們會把藥糊涂滿你肚皮
We're gonna rub it all over your belly,
然后你就會好受多了
and it's gonna make you feel better.
這藥膏涂到吐司上再配個煎蛋 味道也不錯哦
It's also not terrible on toast with a fried egg.
外面到底有多少人
How many people are out there?!
就幾個來支持你的女性
Just a few supportive women.
姐妹們好啊
Hello, sisters.
我一定是發錯群聊了
I must've texted the wrong thread.
請讓我跟大地女神談談
Allow me to talk to the Earth Goddess.
莉莉 我是繼小叔曼尼啦
Lily? Step-Uncle Manny's here.
珍惜這個
Cherish this.
你被賦予了創造生命的能力
You've been given the ability to create life.
每一下痙攣 每一次偏頭痛都提醒你...
Each cramp, each migraine should remind you --
你他媽給我滾遠點 曼尼
Get the out of here, Manny!
保重 各位
Take care, everybody.
好
Yeah.
克萊爾 進來
Claire, get in here.
面試進行得如何
How'd the interview go?
順利極了
Amazing.
首先 那地方彌漫著香味
First of all, that place smells delicious.
他們當場就決定聘請我
They made me an offer on the spot.
當首席執行官 有公費旅行
CEO, travel...
跟國會議員們打交道
hobnobbing with Congressmen.
我不意外
Well, I'm not surprised.
你是名出色的候選人
You're a terrific candidate.
我拒絕了
I turned them down.
為什么
Why?
首先 因為我對這里每個人還有你
Well, first of all, because I made a commitment
做出過承諾
to everyone here and to you.
而且 離開這里感覺不對
And it just... didn't feel right to leave.
你這么說 讓我接下來要說的話略顯尷尬
That makes what I'm about to say awkward.
我準備辭職
I'm quitting.
怎么 你有那么氣我嗎
Oh, wha-- You're that mad at me?
不 我聽了你說的
No, I listened to what you said,
除非我讓位 否則你永遠不會
and you're never truly gonna be in charge
真正掌管公司
until I get out of your way.
你不必為了我這么做啊
You didn't have to do that for me.
我不只是為了你
I didn't do it just for you.
每個優秀的衣柜家都知道何時該高高掛起
Every good closet man knows when to hang it up.
我認為 我準備好迎接新挑戰了
And I -- I think I'm ready for a new challenge.
爸爸 可別去搞玻璃貼膜啊
Oh, Dad, not window tinting.
做那個可好賺了 不過不是 那不適合我
It's like printing money, but no, it's not for me.
我興奮期待的是這個
Here's what I'm excited about.
我給你看看
Let me show you. Mm.
這是什么鬼
What am I looking at?
未來
The future.
趣味狗狗床
Fun dog beds.
天啊 這就是你之前在鬼畫符的菠蘿
Oh, my God. This is the pineapple you were doodling.
沒錯 是我親自設計的
Yes! I designed it myself!
酷 酷
Cool. Cool.
話說 藥房會跟進
So, the pharmacy tracks
你吃的藥如何相互影響的 對吧
how all of your medications interact, right?
克萊爾 每年
Claire, every year,
全美人民會花七百億美元在寵物身上
people in this country spend $70 billion on their pets.
全美人民還是就你一人
People or just you?
我已經找好制造商了
I got a manufacturer lined up.
我會在網上賣 節省總開銷
I'll sell them online, keep the overhead low,
去參加一些狗狗大會 超好玩的
go to a bunch of dog shows -- super fun.
如果我出售衣柜公司股份所得到的錢
And if I don't lose all the money that I made
沒有賠個精光
selling my share of this place,
我就很滿意了
I'm happy.
有點像一個時代的終結 對吧
It's kind of the end of an era, huh?
你確定真想這么做嗎
Are you sure you want to do this?
要不是有你 我好多年前就退休了
I'd have quit years ago if you weren't here.
來工作看不到你會感覺很奇怪的
It's gonna be weird coming to work without you.
如果你太想我了
Well, if you miss me too much,
你可以來我的斯黛拉家的狗床工作啊
there'll always be a position for you at Dog Beds by Stella.
多謝了 但我覺得也是時候
Thank you, but I think maybe it is time
證明自己能獨當一面了
I prove myself on my own.
你確定嗎 我這生意可能會一飛沖天呢
You sure? 'Cause this could be huge.
我有無數的狗床點子
I got a million dog-bed ideas.
比如熱狗面包床 太空倉窗
I got a hot-dog bun, I got a space capsule,
還有愛斯基摩人冰屋
I got an igloo.
那狗骨頭形狀的床呢
What about one shaped like a dog bone?
總有一天你也會跟上我的腳步
You'll get there.
莉莉怎么樣了
Hey, how's Lily doing?
我壓根就沒幫上忙 還讓情況惡化了
Well, I certainly didn't help. I only made it worse.
當我們孩子也需要我的時候 我該怎么辦啊
What am I gonna do when our kids need me?
你多慮了
You're overthinking it.
等你看到他們可愛的小臉蛋向你尋求幫助時
The minute you see a sweet little face that needs you,
你的直覺就會讓你知道該怎么做
your instincts will kick in, and you'll know what to do.
大家都這么說
That's what everybody keeps saying,
萬一到時候不是這樣怎么辦
but what if it's not true?
鄧菲先生
Hey, Mr. D.
你還好嗎
Hey. Are you okay?
我好多天沒睡了
I haven't slept for days,
今天還搞砸了工作上的事
and I screwed up at work today.
肯定沒有你覺得的這么糟糕啦
Oh, I'm sure it's not as bad as you think.
攝影師說這就像節目《搞砸舞臺》
Well, the cameraman called it "Disaster-piece Theatre,"
然后大家都說"說到點子上啦 克萊格"
and everybody was like, "Good one, Craig."
有毛病嗎 沒毛病 說到點子上了 克萊格
And you know what? It was. It was a good one, Craig.
沒事的啦
Hey, it's okay.
我明天得再花錢
I had to rehire the crew
重新雇拍攝組來拍一次
to shoot the whole thing again tomorrow.
預算大超支
I'm way over budget.
估計也保不住這間待售屋...
I'm probably gonna lose the listing --
你只是累昏頭了
You're just overtired.
要不你先把眼睛閉上
Why don't you close your eyes?
迪蘭 制造一點助眠的白噪音
Dylan, make some white noise.
我來試一招
I am going to try something.
挺舒服的
Oh. That's nice.
寶貝
Honey.
你越來越拿手了呢
You're getting really good at this.
你真這么覺得嗎
You think so?
真的
I do.
謝謝
Thanks.
好啦 你現在就好好休息
All right. You just rest now.
一切都會船到橋頭自然直
Everything's gonna be okay.
會的
Yeah. It is.
我可以停下了嗎 我快缺氧暈過去了
Can I stop now? I'm gonna pass out.
我們可以撬開鎖然后把她弄出來
We could just pick the lock and get her out of there.
然后呢 她出來了也不會想跟我們說話
And then what? She doesn't want to talk to us.
她從小就從不跟我們談 我們以前也沒停過手
She never wants to talk to us. That hasn't stopped us before.
我們這次停手
We're only letting it now
只不過是因為自己覺得話題尷尬罷了
because we're uncomfortable, right?
很明顯是你說的這樣
Obviously, you're right.
不然我為什么會大吃特吃歌洛莉亞的藥糊
Why else would I be devouring Gloria's poultice?
我決定了
You know what?
來吧 我們是她爸爸
Come on. We're her dads.
我們會想出辦法的
We'll figure something out.
親愛的
Hey, honey?
大家都走啦
Everyone's gone.
對不起 我們讓你羞恥了
And we're sorry we embarrassed you.
我們就不應該拉這么多人來參與...
We should've never included all those people into...
這件事情
this situation.
盡管我們是男生 不代表我們...
And just because we're boys doesn't mean we --
我們就不能陪你談你首次...
we can't talk you through your first...
"子宮內膜脫落"
"Sloughing off of your endometrial tissue."
是啊"這通常會持續二到....
Yeah, "Which typically lasts between two and...
-七天" -七天嗎
- seven days"? - Seven?
-天啊 -要人命了
- Oh, my God. - That's crazy.
聽我說 莉莉 你從小到大 一直都...
Look, Lily, your whole life, it's been --
一直都是我們三個人一起摸索與成長
it's been the three of us figuring out stuff together.
對啊 你忘了嗎 在你二年級的時候
Yeah, don't you remember in the -- in the second grade,
你哭著回家 因為同學朱莉·關
when you came home crying because Julie Kwan made fun
取笑你的瑞奇·馬丁熱單午餐盒嗎
of your Ricky Martin "She Bangs" lunch box?
你一開始也不想聊 但后來怎么著
You didn't want to talk about that, but then,
你最后跟我們聊了之后 不是好受許多嗎
when you finally did, you felt better.
對啊 你... 你不用自己獨自面對這一切
Yeah, you -- you don't have to figure this out alone.
我們或許沒有跟你一模一樣的經歷
Yeah, we may not have gone through the exact same thing,
但你知道嗎 在七年級的時候
but, you know, in the seventh grade,
我們男生的身體也會起變化啊
our bodies started changing, too.
我是六年級開始的
Sixth for me.
這又不是比賽
It's not a competition.
而那些改變
And those changes...
也很讓我們困惑
they were confusing.
是啊 它們讓人感到困窘又可怕
Yeah, they were con-- confusing and scary
但也很...
and also, um...
令人興奮 因為...
exciting because, um...
那也表示你在長大 莉莉
you're growing up... Lily.
我們是你的父母
And we're your parents, okay?
我們肯定會犯錯
We are gonna make mistakes,
我們也不知道所有問題的答案
and we are not gonna have all the answers,
但當你想要聊問題與困難的時候
but when you do want to talk about it,
我們... 我們都會在這陪你
we're -- we're here for you.
是的
Yeah.
我們愛你
We love you.
糟糕 偉大的魔術師睡迪尼來了
Uh-oh. Here comes The Great Snoozedini.
在你們面前有三個普通的杯子
You see before you three ordinary cups.
可以在任何人家里廚房找到的杯子
Cups you'd find in any kitchen.
沒有任何特殊的地方
Nothing magical about them.
現在我們拿起一個新的土豆
Here, we have one new potato.
請緊盯放了土豆的杯子
Keep your eye on the cup with the potato.
有外地來看表演的朋友嗎
Anybody here from out of town?
不忍直視 我們該不該把他叫醒啊
I feel bad. Should we wake him up?
等我們找到土豆在哪個杯子里再叫醒他
Not until we find out where the potato is.
是在那個杯子里吧
It's under that one, right?
土豆在這個杯子里嗎
Is the potato here?
這個魔術好...
Oh, this trick is a real...
檸檬啊
lemon.
大家晚安
Good night everyone.
太厲害了
Amazing.